Alexander (Sasha) Goldberg

Email- sashagol54@gmail.com Phone- +972525562439

Summary

I have 9 years of experience in Algorithmic Trading (4 years in traditional markets and 5 years in Crypto Markets). During that time I gained knowledge in managing, operating, and monitor large and complex trading operations and combining risk management to ensure effective operation.

Skills Highlights

- Finance & Accounting
- Strategy
- Risk Management

- Team Management
- Entrepreneurial
- Traditional and crypto markets

Experience

Keyrock, Head of Markets, Brussels (department of 14 quant traders) - 07/2020 - 06/2021

- Monitor, operate and optimize running markets according to objectives
- Design and build the tools necessary to operate markets at scale
- Keep track of all inventory under management
- Coordinating with multiple departments (research, development, and commercial)

Efficient Frontier (crypto algo firm), Senior Trading Specialist, Tel Aviv 04/2019 - 07/2020

- Built the spot market making division from recruitment to work protocols
- Responsible for managing PNL and KPI's, building strategies and improving monitoring tools of the operation with the development team
- Conducting research for profitable market making and also to find opportunities in derivatives

C.W.M Solutions, Co Founder and Co CEO, Tel Aviv – 02/2018 to 03/2019

- Developed the company from day one
- Responsible for the ongoing management and finances
- Managed the trading and liquidation operations by using technical analyses, fundamental research, back testing of recorded data in order to check strategies and to create risk management module

I.R.R (traditional markets Algo firm), Operation manager, Tel Aviv - 01/2015 to 09/2018

- Operate and supervise trading systems
- Monitor fundamental news and work alongside brokers to manage positions

Education & Certificates

The College of Management – BA in Accounting and Business Administration – 2012 to 2016 **Military Services** – Combatant and Commander in the IDF, Nahal Brigade Battalion 932 2006-2009

Languages (CEFR levels)